[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 27, "question": "There's no political tea leaves to be read here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 28, "answer": "We don't have any tea.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 117, "question": "What was your assessment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 118, "answer": "Well, I think that she engaged.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 136, "question": "And is there any doubt that she'll run in 2016?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 137, "answer": "I think there -- I think there's a doubt.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2016"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "And I suppose the key question is, what do you collectively think can actually be achieved here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "Well, I thought it was an excellent meeting, and it went beyond just the narrow topic of assault weapons into the broader topic of gun violence in general.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 183, "question": "Or is it true that the majority of American people don't really want one?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "Well, from my personal perspective and what we dealt with in some of the things I have seen over 28 years in law enforcement, I personally don't think banning any weapon is going to stop the problem.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "130128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "Do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "Well, the problem that I see that we're missing here is we have a situation that because we're talking about gun violence at the forefront, we're missing the issue that I think is really paramount throughout all of America.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 222, "question": "Explain to me how you think the best way of dealing with the handgun issue could be going forward?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 223, "answer": "When you say the best way, obviously, you have to look at things that are possible.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 230, "question": "Do you see any reason why you need to have assault rifles in civilian hands generally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 231, "answer": "I don't see a reason for it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ":", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "How do you try and deal with that mentality in a reasonable way that doesn't offend gun owners but actually works to reduce the total volume of guns rather than dramatically increase it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "ELLY: The Second Amendment is here to stay.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York City"]}, "docId": "130128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 250, "question": "Can any of these laws -- from a law enforcement perspective, can any of them be properly effective if they are not federal laws?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "MD", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 251, "answer": "Ninety percent of the guns that we confiscate here on the streets of New York City are coming from out of state.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "VBN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "Is it time for more politicians to show a bit of backbone and a bit of personal courage over this rather than worrying about their political futures?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "JJR", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "Yes, I don't think it's too much to ask for our elected officials to vote your conscience.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 306, "question": "How do we get this debate to the correct place where real action can be done that will have real effects on curbing gun violence?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "Well, that's exactly the 64,000 dollar question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 336, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "I don't accept that you have to start some place.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 349, "question": "Isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 350, "answer": "Well, that's supposing that their conscious tells them that's the right thing to do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "But do you agree that the answer to gun violence is categorically not to reduce the volume of guns in circulation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "Yes, I do agree.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "130128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "And yet you're aware that obviously every country that has brought in tough gun control, almost without exception, around the world, from Japan to Australia to Britain, has seen dramatic reductions in the amount of gun murders and gun-related crimes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "NNP", "TO", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "Right, but if you look at -- the United States isn't even in the top ten of leaders in the category of violent crimes, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Japan", "Australia", "Britain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 400, "question": "Presumably -- I mean, do you agree or disagree with the ban on machine guns, for example, automatic machine guns?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "CC", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 401, "answer": "Well, that's a reasonable restriction.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "And that's why I don't understand why you're comfortable with banning one and not the other?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "CD", "CC", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "It's not a question of what I'm comfortable with.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "What is the difference?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "The AR-15 is semiautomatic, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 493, "question": "Dana, other -- Dana, other than keeping guns in people's hand -- I have your point on that -- what would you proactively do to reduce gun violence?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", ":", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "POS", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", ":", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "Tougher penalties for criminals who kill people with illegally obtained fire arms.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dana"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 496, "question": "Did that answer your question?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "JJR", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "Charles --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]